If that still doesn't work,
I still have the Mei Family's Celestial Seal.
Rat!
That's enough, Young Master.
Don't waste your breath.
These two are as stubborn
as a Jiangshi that's been in a coffin
for ten thousand years.
It's you.
The one in the coffin.
Young Master, it's one thing to touch their seal,
but why did you have to disturb the person in the coffin too?
When you trespassed into the Mei Family's secret room earlier,
I was fully aware.
The reason I hid in the coffin
was to hear exactly what you were up to.
It seems the Sheng Family really got a fine live-in son-in-law.
Return it to its rightful owner.
Miss Mei,
borrowing the seal was indeed a bit offensive.
But right now, I can't comply.
Fine.
You can keep the Celestial Seal.
On one condition.
You become a live-in son-in-law to the Mei Family as well,
and be my husband.
Isn't that just Selling oneself?
You're
after
my fate constitution, aren't you?
You want me on the Mei Family's way to the Tidal Tomb,
to shield you from disasters.
And what if I refuse?
If you refuse?
You won't walk out of this alley.
Then I accept.
I accept it.
Alright, let him go.
He's one of us now.
Dad,
the full moon is approaching.
The Sheng Family is currently Leaderless.
As for our Qi Family,
as their long-standing family allies,
shouldn't we go and help them?
Help?
Of course we must help them.
But how exactly we help,
that requires tact.
I'm organizing a Sheng Family friends and family care team.
Our people will step forward
to help them stabilize the situation.
Oh, right.
Especially in places like the storehouse
and the accounting room,
we must deploy extra manpower
to focus on protecting them
and pay extra attention.
Don't worry, Dad. I promise
our care team will act Like a spring breeze and rain,
silently getting the job done.
I guarantee the Sheng Family will be Moved to tears.
The boy is worth teaching.
Young Master,
there's something I don't understand.
Why did Miss Mei insist on you being a live-in son-in-law?
What does she see in you?
What does she want from you?
Or does she think you're an experienced live-in son-in-law?
Didn't you agree to it?
If I didn't agree,
we'd be just like that Puppet Corpse.
Let's go.
Let's play along with the Qi Family's little show first.
Tiankun,
we're going there to help.
Remember to keep it dignified.
Understood, Dad.
Zhang Tianyou.
How bold of you.
I was just looking for you,
and here you are delivering yourself to my door.
Dad, let me kill him.
Don't be hasty.
I'm
here to apologize.
Eldest Young Master Qi kept climbing my wall for no reason,
and ended up injuring his leg...
I'm deeply sorry for that.
Can you afford to compensate for my son's leg?
I'd like to see
what you'll use to compensate.
With this.
There's a prescription in the Earth Vein Sutra.
It's said to cure Eldest Young Master Qi's leg,
letting him experience the feeling of walking on solid ground again.
Don't be impulsive.
Let's talk about your terms.
The Sheng Family's territory is too small.
It's shabby.
I want
this piece.
Dad, he's crazy!
Fine.
Prepare the contract.
Thank you.
I'll take my leave.
Let's go.
Guards!
Master Qi, you're pulling a double-cross?
Trying that with me?
You're still too green.
You think I scare that easily?
You really think that's dynamite?
Get them!
Dad, are you okay?
Illusion technique.
This kid actually has some Spiritual Power.
I still underestimated him.
With our two families fighting,
I was afraid the Wan Family and Mei Family would interfere.
Since this kid has a death wish,
no one can save him.
We can't let him die at the Qi Family,
nor can we let him die at the Sheng Family.
Dad, then where should he die?
Out on the road.
Go now.
Understood. I'll go right now.
How did I raise such an idiot?
Wait, Young Master.
Did you really give it to him?
No.
There they are. Catch them!
Let's go.
Over there!
Second Young Master, I found them!
Those two idiots.
A bunch of trash.
Why aren't you attacking?
Look at you cowards.
Give me the blade.
Why is there no blood?
What are you?
Qi the Second.
You were willing to see me,
which means you agreed.
Yeah.
Qi Tiankun.
And who's this beauty?
Where did she pop up from?
Don't you dare touch the Mei Family's new Young Master!
Let's fall back!
Zhang Tianyou!
You just wait!
Come on, get back here!
Come here.
Don't they need to see a doctor?
They're perfectly fine!
Father.
What are you doing?
Don't worry, Tianting.
With our Qi Family's Talisman Book,
and the Sheng Family's Sutra,
I will definitely heal your legs.
Will this really work?
It definitely will!
How's it going, son? Feeling it now?
Dad.
Dad...
I don't feel anything.
That's impossible.
Which step went wrong?
Why don't you check again?
Son.
I skipped a verse.
Sorry about that.
I'll do it again right now.
It'll definitely work.
We, The Four Great Families, have already agreed
to choose a Dragon-Seeking Champion
to lead us back to the Tidal Tomb from twenty years ago,
to eliminate the root cause that's plagued us for over twenty years.
But this Champion
must be an outsider,
and must possess a special fate constitution.
Originally, my Mei Family
had already chosen someone for me:
a Yin-hour born with a strong enough fate constitution.
Who?
Li Xiao.
The son of the warlord Marshal Li.
My Mei Family originally wanted to use their influence
to retire from the underworld
and go legitimate.
I was actually ready to accept my fate.
But then I found out
that while Li Xiao was arranging our marriage,
he was having a clandestine affair with Miss Wan Chun'er of the Wan Family.
He thought I was some clay Buddha in a temple,
without any temper.
So you found me, the live-in son-in-law of the Sheng Family,
to act as a shield.
Just to spite him.
Well, you can't exactly put it that way.
It's just that someone has to fill this position.
As for whether it's a pig or a dog,
as long as it's not Li Xiao,
I can probably tolerate it.
Miss Mei,
your way of complimenting people
is really quite unique.
You flatter me.
The Celestial Seal is already in your hands.
I hope my desperate act of grasping at straws
wasn't misplaced.
Becoming the Champion of the four families
and gathering the Talisman, Curse, Seal, and Eye is only the first step.
I will personally find that tomb and destroy it.
But the ones who could use the Dragon-Seeking Formula
to find the Tidal Tomb, the Dragon-Seeking Zhang Family,
disappeared over twenty years ago.
You only have a Dragon-Seeking Ruler.
Will that be enough?
That's my business.
Zhang Tianyou.
Who exactly are you?
Dad!
How is it, son?
You feel it, right?
Master.
This... This feels like...
Take a look!
Dad!
How is it, Dad?
Tianting.
Why are you fooling around?
Why did you put your hand down here?
I grabbed the wrong hand.
My hand isn't down there.